New York Review of Books Records
New York Review of Books Records
1963-1969
New York Review of Books.
14.6 linear ft.
Correspondence, incoming and outgoing, of the publisher, advertising manager, and business manager; production papers consisting of editorial, printing, distribution, and advertising records, including review assignment sheets; financial and legal papers, including authors' payment lists, bank statements, budgets, contracts, cost estimates, and remittance lists; and manuscripts, includings tables of contents for various issues, lists of contributors, articles, book reviews, letters, movie reviews, poems, and theater reviews, mainly revised printers' copies.
149391
Biographical History
The New York Review of Books was begun in New York City in February, 1963. Among those primarily responsible for its inception were Robert Silvers, then on the staff of Harper's Magazine, Barbara Epstein and her husband, Jason Epstein, an editor for Random House, and Elizabeth Hardwick, wife of poet Robert Lowell. The immediate reason for its publication was the newspaper strike, which eliminated one of the means by which publishers advertised their new works to the book-buying market and made them eager for some substitute outlet for such publicity. But there was also a longer range reason--belief that a large audience existed for extensive and critical reviews of books which was not being satisfied by the New York Times.Book Review section or the Saturday Review. The strike provided the ideal opportunity to test the demand for and acceptance of such a book reviewing medium.
Many well-known writers and scholars were convinced to write reviews for nothing, and the first issue was financed by sales of advertising space to publishers. This issue was widely acclaimed as a breath of fresh air for the literary world and sold out rapidly. Its success prompted the founders to attempt a second issue, which also met with praise and produced a comparable sales record. The response accorded both issues thus confirmed them in the decision to begin publication on a continuing basis, and the first regular issue appeared in August, 1963. The format was then, as it is now, a bi-monthly tabloid containing articles, extensive and critical book reviews, poetry, advertisements for the book trade, and other items of literary interest.
The decision to publish on a regular basis necessitated additions to the staff. Among those who now became associated with the venture was A. Whitney Ellsworth, formerly on the staff of the Atlantic Monthly, who took on the responsibilities of publisher.
The circulation of the magazine grew to sixty thousand in 1966 and a survey at that time showed that most of the readership was college educated -- a sizeable percentage also having had some graduate education -- urban, affluent, and highly literate. A large percentage of the readers were associated with universities in one way or another. Approximately forty per cent were concentrated in New England and the middle-Atlantic states, with another sixteen per cent on the Pacific coast.
During the middle sixties, the NYRB became more involved in politics. Articles, reviews and David Levine caricatures were increasingly critical of American culture, society, and foreign policy. The increased opposition to the Vietnam war prompted the NYRB to send Mary McCarthy to South Vietnam for reports on and observations about American involvement there. She also went to North Vietnam in order to describe the effect of the war on the people and government of that country. This involvement in radical politics brought the NYRB a certain amount of notoriety. It would be false to say that it became completely politicized, however, for side by side with radical polemics there continued to be reviews of books on art, music, and literature.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The New York Review of Books Records, 1963-1969, include correspondence, production papers, financial and legal papers, manuscripts, and a miscellany.
Correspondence, 1963-1969, consists of incoming and outgoing letters of the publisher, advertising manager, and business managers. It includes routine business correspondence dealing with printing, distribution, subscription fulfillment, subscribers list exchanges, subscribers' complaints, advertising, and various sales promotions.
Production papers, 1963-1969, consist of editorial printing, distribution, and advertising records. The editorial records include review assignment sheets and various materials related to the publication by the NYRB of Herbert Kohl's Teaching the Unteachables. The printing records consist of invoices which detail the printing costs for each issue, a printing cost analysis, press run statistics, and publication schedules. The distribution records include invoices for fulfillment services, return reports of unsold newsstand copies, and miscellaneous field reports on newsstand sales.
Advertising records consist of an ad prospectus, a readership survey, and a sample of various ad layouts.
Financial and legal papers, 1963-1968, include authors' payment lists, bank statements, contracts, remittance lists and reprint statements from Editor's Choice (an outside business which handles requests for reprinting of material from NYRB), remittance advices from Capital Distributing Company, and some miscellaneous materials. The authors' payment lists consist of lists of writers and reviewers printed in every issue and the amount paid to them for their work. The remittance schedules and reprint lists from Editor's Choice consist of monthly statements to NYRB regarding which of its materials have been reprinted, and the amount paid for permission to reprint. Of interest among the miscellaneous materials are various budgets and cost estimates.
Manuscripts, 1963-1968, consist of tables of contents for various issues, lists of contributors, articles, book reviews, letters, movie reviews, poems, and theater reviews. Most of the manuscripts are typescript revised printer's copies. Included at the end are miscellaneous articles, book reviews, letters, and poems which either could not be assigned by the processor to a particular issue or were not used by the editors, as well as some unidentifiable fragments.
Because all print issues of the New York Review of Books are freely available -- both for searching and browsing -- on the NYRB's website at http://www.nybooks.com/issues/, the chronological listing of manuscripts does not include names of authors or of books reviewed. Authors and titles are, however, given for unpublished and unused manuscripts.
Authors and reviewers whose work occurs most frequently among these manuscripts are the following:
Robert M. Adams, Henry David Aiken, Noel Annan, Hannah Arendt, Neal Ascherson, W.H. Auden
Geoffrey Barraclough, Bernard Bergonzi, Marius Bewley
J.M. Cameron, Noam Chomsky, Louis A. Coser
Denis Donoghue, F.W. Dupee
D.J. Enright, Jason Epstein
Marius I. Finley, R.W. Flint, Edgar Z. Friedenberg
E.H. Gombrich, Paul Goodman
Stuart Hampshire, Elizabeth Hardwick, Francis Haskell, Robert Heilbroner, Matthew Hodgart, Irving Howe
D.A.N. Jones
Alfred Kazin, Murray Kempton, J.P. Kenyon, Frank Kermode
Walter Laqueur, Christopher Lasch, George Lichtheim
Robert Mazzocco, Mary McCarthy, Hans Morgenthau, Helen Muchnic
Conor Cruise O'Brien
J.H. Plumb, V.S. Pritchett
Phillip Rahv, Christopher Ricks
Ronald Steel, I.F. Stone, Lawrence Stone
A.J.P. Taylor, J. Thompson, H.R. Trevor-Roper
Gore Vidal
J. Weightman
Frances Yates
Miscellany, 1965-1970, includes galley page proofs of a book which appears to have been annotated by a reviewer, but for which no review was found, and a typescript carbon draft of a book of memoirs which seems never to have been used. It also includes various printed indices to the Review.
Arrangement of the Collection
Correspondence, advertising records and financial and legal papers are arranged chronologically.
Within the production papers, editorial records are arranged chronologically; printing and distribution records are arranged alphabetically by type and chronologically within that order.
Manuscripts are arranged chronologically according to the date of the issue in which they appeared, alphabetically by type of material, and alphabetically by author within the various types, except that tables of contents and contributors lists are always placed first. Miscellaneous unused items are placed at the end, arranged first by type (e.g., poems, reviews, etc.) and then alphabetically by author.
Miscellany at the end is arranged alphabetically by author.
Related Material
All print issues of the New York Review of Books are freely available -- both for searching and browsing -- on the NYRB's website at http://www.nybooks.com/issues/.
Subject and Genre Headings
Literature -- American Fiction; Literature -- American Poetry; Popular culture; Publishing, printing and book arts; New York Review of Books.; The New York Review of Books.; Books -- Reviews -- Periodicals.; Periodicals -- Publishing.; Publishers and publishing -- United States.; Articles.; Book reviews.; Budgets.; Contracts.; Correspondence.; Financial records.; Galley proofs.; Manuscripts for publication.; Publishers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the New York Review of Books, 1969.
Inventory
- Correspondence
  - Publisher
    - 1963-1965, 10 folders (Box 1)
    - 1966, 12 folders (Box 2)
    - January 1967-October 1967, 10 folders (Box 3)
    - November 1967-1968, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Advertising manager, 1963; 1965,; 1967,; undated (Box 4)
  - Business manager, 1965-1969; 2 folders (Box 4)
- Production papers
  - Editorial records
    - Book review assignment lists, 5 folders (Box 4)
    - Kohl, Herbert, Teaching the "Unteachables", 1967
      - Manuscript, typescript and typescript copy and typescript repro and printed material repro and typescript copy, revised (Box 4)
      - Cost projections and cost estimates (Box 4)
      - Background materials for Carnegie Foundation proposal, letters of announcement (Box 4)
      - Letters of praise (possible use for publicity), typescript reproduction and holograph reproduction and holograph and typescript (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous related materials, published material and typescript reproduction (Box 4)
  - Printing records
    - Invoices, 1963-1966; 4 folders (Box 4)
    - Invoices, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Cost analysis of printing, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Press run statistics, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
    - Publication schedules, 1964-1968 (Box 5)
  - Distribution records
    - Fulfillment services
      - James Watson and Co.
        - Billing schedules, undated (Box 5)
        - Fulfillment cost analysis, 1964-1966 (Box 5)
        - Invoices, 1963-1966; 3 folders (Box 5)
        - Proposed source coding schedule, 1965 (Box 5)
      - Creative Contract Services
        - Invoices, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous notes on fulfillment problems, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Return reports
      - Capital Distributing Co., 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Field reports on newsstand sales, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
      - Material relating to circulation, undated, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Advertising records
    - Advertising prospectus (subscriptions), 1967 (Box 5)
    - Readership survey, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Ad copy, sample ad brochures, ad orders, 1963; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Ad copy and layout (Brentano's ad), 1964 (Box 5)
    - Ad copy, 1966-1967 (Box 5)
    - Ad copy (Mary McCarthy in Vietnam), 1967 (Box 5)
    - Comments on first publication of NYRB, 1963 (Box 5)
- Financial and legal papers
  - Authors' payments, 1963-1967; 4 folders (Box 5)
  - Bank statements
    - Chase-Manhattan Bank, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Marine Midland Trust Co., 1963-1964 (Box 5)
    - Marine Midland Trust Co., circulation, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Contracts, 1964-1968; undated (Box 6)
  - Copyright registration certificate, 1963 (Box 6)
  - Editor's Choice
    - Remittance schedule for reprints, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Reprint list, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Remittance advices
    - Capital Distributing Co., 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Statement of insurance coverage, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Financial material (budgets, cost estimates), 1963-1964 (Box 6)
    - Sales figures for February 1963 issue (Box 6)
    - Sales reports, David Levine buttons, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Statement of ownership, publisher's statement, 1965 (Box 6)
- Manuscripts
  Because all print issues of the New York Review of Books are freely available -- both for searching and browsing -- on the NYRB's website at http://www.nybooks.com/issues/, the chronological listing of manuscripts does not include names of authors or of books reviewed. Authors and titles are, however, given for unpublished and unused manuscripts.
  - 1963 Aug 29 (Box 6)
  - 1963 Sep 12, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - 1963 Sep 26, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - 1963 Oct 17, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - 1963 Oct 31 (Box 7)
  - 1963 Nov 6 (Box 7)
  - 1963 Nov 28 (Box 7)
  - 1963 Dec 12 (Box 7)
  - 1963 Dec 26, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - 1964 Jan 9, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - 1964 Jan 23 (Box 7)
  - 1964 Feb 6 (Box 8)
  - 1964 Feb 20 (Box 8)
  - 1964 Mar 5, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - 1964 Mar 19 (Box 8)
  - 1964 Apr 2 (Box 8)
  - 1964 Apr 16 (Box 8)
  - 1964 Apr 30 (Box 8)
  - 1964 May 14 (Box 8)
  - 1964 May 28, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - 1964 Jun 11, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - 1964 Jun 25 (Box 9)
  - 1964 Jul 9, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - 1964 Jul 30, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - 1964 Aug 20 (Box 9)
  - 1964 Sep 10, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - 1964 Sep 24 (Box 10)
  - 1964 Oct 8 (Box 10)
  - 1964 Oct 22, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - 1964 Nov 5 (Box 10)
  - 1964 Nov 19, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - 1964 Dec 3, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - 1964 Dec 17 (Box 10)
  - 1964 Dec 31 (Box 11)
  - 1965 Jan 14 (Box 11)
  - 1965 Jan 28, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - 1965 Feb 11 (Box 11)
  - 1965 Feb 25 (Box 11)
  - 1965 Mar 11 (Box 11)
  - 1965 Mar 25 (Box 11)
  - 1965 Apr 8, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - 1965 Apr 22, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - 1965 May 6, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - 1965 May 20 (Box 12)
  - 1965 Jun 3, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - 1965 Jun 17 (Box 12)
  - 1965 Jul 1, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - 1965 Jul 15 (Box 13)
  - 1965 Aug 5 (Box 13)
  - 1965 Aug 26, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - 1965 Sep 16 (Box 13)
  - 1965 Sep 30, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - 1965 Oct 14, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - 1965 Oct 28, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - 1965 Nov 11, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 1965 Nov 25, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 1965 Dec 9, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 1965 Dec 23, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 1966 Jan 6 (Box 14)
  - 1966 Jan 20, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 1966 Feb 3 (Box 14)
  - 1966 Feb 17 (Box 15)
  - 1966 Mar 17 (Box 15)
  - 1966 Mar 31, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 1966 Apr 14, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 1966 Apr 28, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 1966 May 12, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 1966 May 26, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 1966 Jun 9 (Box 16)
  - 1966 Jun 23, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - 1966 Jul 7, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - 1966 Jul 28 (Box 16)
  - 1966 Aug 18 (Box 16)
  - 1966 Sep 8 (Box 16)
  - 1966 Sep 22 (Box 16)
  - 1966 Oct 6, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 1966 Oct 20, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 1966 Nov 3 (Box 17)
  - 1966 Nov 17, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 1966 Dec 1 (Box 17)
  - 1966 Dec 15, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 1966 Dec 29, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 1967 Jan 12 (Box 18)
  - 1967 Jan 26, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 1967 Feb 9 (Box 18)
  - 1967 Feb 23, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - 1967 Mar 9, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - 1967 Mar 23, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 1967 Apr 6, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - 1967 Apr 20 (Box 20)
  - 1967 May 18 (Box 20)
  - 1967 Jun 1, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - 1967 Jun 15, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - 1967 Jun 29, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - 1967 Jul 13, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - 1967 Aug 3, 3 folders (Box 22)
  - 1967 Aug 24, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - 1967 Sep 14, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - 1967 Sep 28, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - 1967 Oct 12, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - 1967 Oct 26 (Box 24)
  - 1967 Nov 9, 3 folders (Box 25)
  - 1967 Dec 21, 3 folders (Box 25)
  - 1968 Jan 4 (Box 25)
  - 1968 Jan 18, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - 1968 Feb 1, 3 folders (Box 26)
  - 1968 Feb 15, 3 folders (Box 26)
  - 1968 Feb 29, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 1968 Mar 14, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - 1968 Mar 29, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - 1968 Apr 11 (Box 27)
  - 1968 Apr 25, 4 folders (Box 28)
  - 1968 May 9, 3 folders (Box 28)
  - 1968 May 23, 3 folders (Box 29)
  - 1968 Jun 6, 3 folders (Box 29)
  - 1968 Jun 20, 3 folders (Box 30)
  - 1968 Jul 11, 3 folders (Box 30)
  - 1968 Aug 01, 3 folders (Box 31)
  - 1968 Aug 22, 3 folders (Box 31)
  - 1968 Sep 12, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - 1968 Sep 26, 4 folders (Box 32)
  - 1968 Oct 10 (Box 32)
  - 1968 Oct 10, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - 1968 Oct 24, 3 folders (Box 33)
  - 1968 Nov 7, 3 folders (Box 33)
  - 1968 Nov 21, 2 folders (Box 34)
  - 1968 Dec 5, 3 folders (Box 34)
  - 1968 Dec 19 (Box 34)
  - 1969 Jan 2 (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous articles, unassignable or unused
    - Brumberg, Abraham, "Poland, Gomulka, and the Jews", typescript reproduction (Box 34)
    - Fruchter, Norman, "A Real Perspective", printed material reproduction (Box 34)
    - Howe, Irving, "Toward a Free, Multi-Racial America", typescript copy (Box 34)
    - Lucas, John, "A Night at the Opera," "Magyar wedding, Irish funeral", typescript revised (Box 34)
    - Park, Clara Claiborne, "Trollope and the Modern Reader", printed material reproduction (Box 34)
    - Prynne, Xavier, "The Gang" (Box 34)
    - Solomon, Barbara Probst, (no title), typescript revised, typescript reproduction revised, typescript reproduction revised (Box 34)
    - Spark, Muriel, "Correspondence and Telephone Dept. of Miss Aurora Cavallo, Novelist", typescript copy (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous book reviews, unassignable or unused
    - A-G
      - Cavell, Stanley, Huxley, Aldous, Literature and Science, typescript revised reproduction (Box 34)
      - Decter, Midge, Mailer Norman, The Presidential Papers, typescript revised reproduction (Box 34)
      - Delaisse, L.M.J., Braunfels, Wolfgang, introduction to, The Lorsch Gospels, typescript revised (Box 34)
      - Enright, D.J., Said, Edward W. Joseph Conrad and the Fiction of Autobiography; Meyer, B.C., Joseph Conrad: A Psychoanalytic Biography; Mudrick, Marvin, ed., Conrad: A Collection of Critical Essays, galley 1, galley 2 (Box 34)
      - Fraser, G.S., Righter, William, Logic and Criticism; Turbayne, Colin Murray, The Myth of Metaphor; Frank, Joseph, The Widening Gyre, typescript revised (Box 34)
      - Gass, Oscar, Scigliano, Robert, South Vietnam: Nation Under Stress; Honey, P.J., Communism in North Vietnam; Fall, Bernard, The Two Viet-nams; Warner, Denis, The Last Confucian; Burchett, Wilfred G., The Furtive War; Tregaskis, Richard, Vietnam Diary; Thai, Nguyen, Is South Vietnam Viable?; Fifield, Russell H., Southeast Asia in United States Policy, typescript revised (Box 34)
      - Geyl, Pieter, Holborn, Hajo, A History of Modern Germany, 1648-1840 (vol. II), holograph and typescript reproduction revised (Box 34)
      - Goldstein, Sally, Blechman, Burt, The War of Camp Omongo; Ludwig, Jack, Confusions; Johnson, Pamela Hansford, Night and Silence Who Is Here: An American Comedy, typescript (Box 34)
      - Goodman, Perceval, Doxiadis, Constantinos A., Architecture in Transition; Wingo, Jr., Lowden, Cities and Space: The Future Use of Urban Land, typescript revised, typescript copy, revised, (incomplete?) (Box 34)
    - H-Z
      - Higgins, Trumbell, Goerlitz, Walter, Paulus and Stalingrad: A Life of Field Marshall Friedrich Paulus; Chuikov, Vasali Ivanovich, The Battle for Stalingrad, typescript revised (Box 35)
      - Hoffman, Stanley, Aron, Robert, France Reborn; White, Dorothy Shipley, Seeds of Discord, typescript revised (Box 35)
      - Johnston, Oswald, Burgess, Anthony, A Clockwork Orange, typescript revised (Box 35)
      - Kolko, Gabriel, Miller, Herman P. Rich Man, Poor Man, typescript revised reproduction (Box 35)
      - Laquer, Walter, Sykes, Christopher, Crossroads To Israel; Litvinoff, Barnet, To the House of Their Fathers; (Pearlman, Moshe), Ben Gurion Looks Back in Talks With Moshe Pearlman, typescript revised, galley (Box 35)
      - Martin Kingsley, Gingham, June, U Thant: The Search For Peace; Kelen, Emery, Hammarskjold, typescript copy revised, galley reproduction revised; also includes author's correspondence (Box 35)
      - Morris, Ivan, Gluck, Jan, ed., Ukiyo: Stories of Post-war Japan, typescript revised (Box 35)
      - Palmer, R.R., Cobban, Alfred, The Social Interpretation of the French Revolution, typescript revised (Box 35)
      - Pryce-Jones, Alan, MacNeice, Lewis, The Strings Are False; Bolton, Isabel, Under Gemini, galley repro revised (Box 35)
      - Scriven, Micheal, Hogben, Lancelot, Science in Authority, holograph, typescript copy revised (Box 35)
      - Sorrentino, Gilbert, Oppenheimer, Joel, The Love Bit, Four Young Lady Poets; Hollo, Anselm, Red Cats; Oppen, George, The Materials; Rexnikoff, Charles, By the Waters of Manhattan; Williams, William Carlos, Pictures from Brueghel; Eshelman, Clayton, Mexico and North; Meltzer, David, We All Have Something to Say To Each Other; Rothenberg, Jerome, The Seven Hells of the Jigoku Zoshi; Spicer, Jack, The Heads of the Town Up to the Aether, published material (Box 35)
      - Waskow, Arthur I., Millis, Walter and Real, James, The Abolition of War; Larson, Arthur ed., A Warless World; Chamberlain, Neil W., The West in a World Without War, typescript revised reproduction (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous letters, unassignable or unused
    - Henry Aaron to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Lionel Abel to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Henry David Aiken reply to Flint (Box 35)
    - Eva Bernhardt to the Editors (incomplete) (Box 35)
    - Conor Cruise O'Brien replies (Box 35)
    - Sally Bird to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Bernard F. Cataldo to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Oscar Collier to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Leonard Conversi to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Robert Flint to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Robert Freeman, Jr. to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Micheal Fried to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Hugh Geeslin, Jr. to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Max Geltman to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Max Gilman to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Harry Goldman to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Amnon Goldworth to the Editors (Box 35)
    - E.H. Gombrich to Bob Silvers, telegram (Box 35)
    - Andrew Hacker reply to Mr. Geeslin (Box 35)
    - Paul Horgan to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Russell Jacoby to the Editors, galley 1 (Box 35)
    - D.A.N. Jones to Bob Silvers (Box 35)
    - Gene G. Kassebaum and Gayathri Rajapur to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Stanley Kauffmann to the Editors (Box 35)
    - John Kinnaird to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Richard Kurman to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Herbert Leibowitz to the Editors (Box 35)
    - S.M. Malkin to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Charles J. Mann to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Laurence Michel to the Editors (Box 35)
    - John Muggeridge to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Hans P. Neisser to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Conor Cruise O'Brien to the Editors (Box 35)
    - William Park to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Leonard Perlman to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Murray Polner to the Editors, holograph (Box 35)
    - Joel Porte to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Dennis Powers to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Charlton Price to the Editors, holograph; revised
    - Richard Reinitz to the Editors (Box 35)
    - James Rieger to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Alan Ritter to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Eugene J. Rosen to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Mark Roskill to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Milton Rugoff to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Andre Ryerson to the Editors (Box 35)
    - J.R. Schuh to the Editors (Box 35)